<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Solar Home System</string>
    <string name="user_name">Yuşa Sarısoy</string>
    <string name="user_mail">myusarisoy@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an account for solar energy payback calculation.</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create account</string>
    <string name="have_an_account">Have an account? Log in</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="surname">Surname</string>
    <string name="mail">Email address</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="login_to">Log in to Solar Home System.</string>
    <string name="login">Log in</string>
    <string name="complete_register">Complete register</string>
    <string name="complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="continueTo">Continue</string>
    <string name="sure_to_sign_out">Are you sure you want to sign out?</string>
    <string name="sure_to_go_back">Are you sure you want to go back? If you do this, your added appliances will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="find_your_account">Find your Solar Home System account</string>
    <string name="enter_your_mail">Enter your email to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset password</string>
    <string name="add_appliance">Please select appliance(s)\nyou want to calculate.</string>
    <string name="click_image">Please click image of an appliance to see its power consumption.</string>
    <string name="grid_choice">Please choose the scenario you want to use.</string>
    <string name="on_grid">On-Grid</string>
    <string name="off_grid">Off-Grid</string>
    <string name="save_appliances">Are you sure to add the appliance(s)?</string>
    <string name="appliances_list">Appliances List</string>
    <string name="no_appliance">Please add at least one appliance to continue.</string>
    <string name="watts">Watts</string>
    <string name="quantity">Quantity</string>
    <string name="hours">Hours</string>
    <string name="find_a_location">Find a location</string>
    <string name="select_a_location">Please select a location where you want to display the solar irradiance data.</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="power_consumption">Power Consumption</string>
    <string name="energy_saver_tips">Energy Saver Tips</string>
    <string name="air_conditioner_consumption_text">If your house has electric heat, you’ll see a big spike on your electricity bill in the middle of winter when you use a lot of power. If you have a heat pump and use it a lot, you may run it somewhere between 10 and 15 hours a day. If your electricity costs 10 cents an hour, that could cost you $15 to $22 a day. The same applies to homes with central air conditioning in the middle of summer.</string>
    <string name="air_conditioner_saver_text">Install a programmable thermostat and set it back at least 10 degrees for eight hours a day. Doing so can save you 10 percent on your energy costs every year, according to the U.S. Department of Energy.</string>
    <string name="water_heater_consumption_text">Water heating uses a good bit of power as well. When you take a shower or run a load of clothes in the washer, the electric water heater might run for an hour reheating the water in the tank. That is 40 cents. A typical household can burn several dollars a day heating water. Because we do not normally think of it this way, it is funny to consider that every shower you take costs 40 cents! When you add in the cost of washing and drying the towels (every load of clothes that you run might cost $1 to $2 for washing and drying), plus the soap and shampoo, it can cost nearly a buck to take a shower!</string>
    <string name="water_heater_saver_text">Shorten your showers and wash your clothes with cold water. You can also set your water heater to at most 120 degrees. Every 10 degree reduction in water heater temperature can save between 3–5 percent in monthly energy costs, according to the U.S. Department of Energy.</string>
    <string name="fridge_consumption_text">Fridges are big-time energy hogs because they use electricity all the time, in many cases for 10 hours or more every day. That comes to about $1 a day, which you can double if you have a second refrigerator or standing freezer.</string>
    <string name="fridge_saver_text">Make sure your refrigerator is set on the optimal temperature and reconsider that extra fridge in the garage.</string>
    <string name="lights_consumption_text">Individual incandescent light bulbs don’t use that much electricity, comparatively speaking, but costs can add up quick. Many light fixtures use more than one bulb and it’s easy to leave lights on throughout your house when you’re not using them. Ten light bulbs use 6 cents an hour. If you use those bulbs for 6 hours a day, it’ll cost you 36 cents a day or about $10 a month. That may not sound like a lot, but $120 a year for lights that you may not be using all the time does.</string>
    <string name="lights_saver_text">Upgrade to energy-efficient CFLs or LEDs when your incandescent bulbs expire. And don’t forget to turn off the lights when you’re not using them.</string>
</resources>
